It's gotten worse.
悪くなってますね
I see...
そうですか…
Your Crime Coefficient's gone up by seven points.
犯罪係数が７ポイント悪化
This is a number we can't ignore.
無視できない数値です
If it gets any worse, I'll be required to report it.
これ以上悪化することがあれば
報告義務が生じます
I've been trying to manage my stress using therapeutic devices.
ヒーリング系の装置で ストレスケアはしているつもりなんですが
You should choose a simpler and more effective method.
もっと単純かつ効果的な方法を取るべきです
Such as?
それは
Talk to someone you're close to about your worries.
親しい人に悩みを相談するんです
Do you have a girlfriend or family?
恋人や家族は
I don't have a girlfriend.
恋人はいません
As for my family...
家族は…
My father is the only one still living.
父だけが存命です
At your age, your father would be an ideal person to talk to.
あなたの年齢なら お父さまは理想的な相談相手ですよ
Unless you have some particular
reason not to, why don't you talk to him?
特殊な事情がなければ
話してみては
Well, I do.
あるんですよ
Yes?
はい？
I do have a reason.
特殊な事情
I would like to show
Cut open my skull
Look into my head
I don't know why I'm so harsh
I could be so brash
I'm going to clash
'Cause I feel
I can always show my everything to you
If this moment was for me
I try to hear, lend my ear
Voices inside
One link to join it all again
'Cause I feel
I can always show my everything to you
If this moment was for me
I try to hear, lend my ear
Voices inside
One link to join it all
So it goes again
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:草泥马 知音   校对:西西   后期:葛蔓
I read the report.
報告書は読んだよ
#13: Invitation from the Abyss
Can we really believe Inspector Tsunemori Akane's testimony?
常守朱監視官の証言だが
あれは本当に信ぴょう性があるのかね
We inspected the scene very carefully.
現場検証は入念に行いました
The distance to the target was a little less than eight meters.
対象までの距離は８ｍ弱
Her position relative to the victim was also clear.
被害者との位置関係も明白です
The crime was clearly committed
right before Inspector Tsunemori's eyes,
犯行は明らかに 常守監視官の目の前で行われ
and yet the Dominator didn't work properly.
そしてドミネーターは正常に作動しなかった
I heard that the victim was a close friend of Inspector Tsunemori.
被害者は常守監視官の親しい友人だそうじゃないか
Is it possible that she was too shaken
up to operate the Dominator correctly?
動転してドミネーターの操作を誤ったのでは
She isn't that incompetent.
彼女はそこまで無能ではありません
You mentioned in one of your
previous reports that she lacks experience.
経験が足りてないと 以前の君の報告書にはあったが
Even so, she possesses genuine aptitude.
だとしても素質は本物です
Her ability as an Inspector has been
proven by the Sibyl System's aptitude test.
監視官としての彼女の能力は
シビュラシステムによる適性診断が証明しています
And yet, you have submitted a report
that questions that same Sibyl's Judgment.
そのシビュラの判定を疑う旨の報告を
君たちは提出しているわけだが…
Ginoza.
宜野座君 この安定した繁栄
Today, the world enjoys a stable prosperity with the
greatest happiness for the greatest number of people.
最大多数の最大幸福が実現された現在の社会を
What do you think makes that possible?
いったい何が支えていると思うかね
That would be... the Ministry of Welfare's Sibyl System.
それは　厚生省のシビュラシステムによるものかと
That's right.
そのとおりだ
Whether in planning one's life,
人生設計　欲求の実現
or obtaining what one desires,
when people make choices, no matter what they are,
今やいかなる選択においても
they ask for Sibyl's Judgment rather than agonize over it.
人々は思い悩むより先にシビュラの判定を仰ぐ
Through the Sibyl System, we create an affluent,
safe world that's unprecedented in human history.
そうすることで
人類の歴史においていまだかつてないほどに豊かで安全な社会を
われわれは成立させている
That's exactly why Sibyl has to be perfect.
だからこそ　シビュラは完璧でなければなりません
Indeed.
しかり シビュラに間違いは許されない
No mistakes are allowed with Sibyl.
That's the ideal.
それが理想だ
However, think about it.
だが考えてもみたまえ
If the system is absolutely perfect,
it shouldn't even require humans to operate it.
もしシステムが完全無欠なら
それを人の手で運用する必要すらないはずだ
We could simply equip the Drones with
Dominators and have them patrol the city.
ドローンにドミネーターを搭載して市内を巡回させればいい
But the Criminal Investigation Department exists within the Bureau,
だが公安局には刑事課が存在し
and you Inspectors and Enforcers
hold the Dominators — Sibyl's eyes.
君たち監視官と執行官が
シビュラの目であるドミネーターの銃把を握っている
Have you thought about why that is?
その意味を考えたことがあるかね
Yes... of course.
それは　むろん…
No matter how perfect the system is made to be,
いかに万全を期したシステムであろうと
it needs a safety net to deal with unforeseeable circumstances.
それでも不測の事態に備えた安全策は必要とされる
When the ability to flexibly respond in an emergency
万が一の柔軟な対応や
機能不全の応急処置
and temporary measures to handle malfunctions
are added, that is when the system becomes perfect.
そうした準備までをも含めて
システムとは完璧なるものとして成立するのだ
For a system such as this,
システムとはね
the most important thing is not that it functions
perfectly, but that people continue to believe that it does.
完璧に機能することよりも
完璧だと信頼され続けることの方が重要だ
Thanks to their belief in the system and sense
of security, Sibyl brings blessings to people even now.
シビュラはその確証と安心感によって
今も人々に恩寵をもたらしている
Understood.
はい
Ginoza.
宜野座君　私は君という男を高く評価している
I think quite highly of you.
Normally, this classified information
wouldn't be accessible to someone of your rank,
本来ならば君の階級では閲覧の許可されない機密情報だが
but I'll show it to you based on the relationship of trust between us.
私と君の信頼関係において見せてやろう
Keep it secret.
他言無用だぞ
This is...
これは…
This is the record of a certain man's arrest.
とある男の逮捕記録だ
He was taken into custody without
his Crime Coefficient being measured...
彼は犯罪係数の計測なしに身柄を確保された
although on the record, he was brought in voluntarily.
記録上はまあ
任意同行ということになっているがね
Touma... Kouzaburou...
藤間 幸三郎…
He's the primary suspect in a serial murder
case that stirred up the public three years ago.
３年前に世間を騒がせた連続殺人の被疑者だ
I think those of you out in the field called it the "Specimen Case".
君たちの現場では
標本事件などと呼ばれていたようだが
In the end, Division 2, who caught
this man, was put under a strict gag order.
結局彼を取り押さえるに至った二係には
徹底したかん口令が敷かれた
Why?! Do you have any idea what we went through to...
なぜです　この男のためにわれわれがどれほど…
It was just like this current case.
今回のケースと同じだよ
Despite the fact that he was practically caught in the
act and we had a great deal of evidence on his crimes,
事実上の現行犯
そしてあらゆる物証の裏付けがあったにもかかわらず
the Dominators didn't react to Touma Kouzaburou...
藤間幸三郎にはドミネーターが反応しなかった
because his Crime Coefficient didn't exceed the regulation limit.
彼の犯罪係数は規定値に達していなかったんだ
We call these rare cases "criminally asymptomatic people".
われわれはこうしたレアケースを「免罪体質者」と呼んでいる
Criminally... asymptomatic?
免罪…体質
It refers to those rare cases where the result of the person's cymatic scan doesn't match with their criminal psychology.
サイマティックスキャンの計測値と犯罪心理が一致しない特殊事例だ
It's estimated that this occurs in
around one out of every two million people.
確率的にはおよそ２００万人に１人の割合で出現しうると予測されている
Makishima Shougo's case isn't really surprising either.
槙島聖護の件についても驚くには値しない
There are some indicatiors that he took
part in the incident from three years ago, right?
この男は３年前の事件にも関与していた節があるのだろう
Touma and Makishima...
藤間と槙島
It is precisely because the two of them, both
criminally asymptomatic, committed the crimes together
２人の免罪体質者が揃って犯行に及んだからこそ
that we had so much difficulty with that case.
あの事件の捜査は難航を極めたわけだ
What happened to Touma Kouzaburou?
藤間幸三郎は どうなったのです
Officially, he's been declared missing.
行方不明と公式には発表されているわけだが
I also do not intend to say anything more on the matter to you.
私もそれ以外のコメントをここで述べるつもりはない
At any rate, all that matters is the fact that no one ever fell victim to his crimes again.
ともあれ重要なのは
彼の犯罪による犠牲者が二度と再び現れることはなかったという事実のみだ
He just disappeared.
彼は　ただ消えたのだ
His case didn't reveal a blind spot in the Sibyl System,
シビュラシステムの盲点を暴くことも
nor did it shake the credibility of the system.
その信頼性を揺るがすこともなく
He simply disappeared.
消えていなくなった
You all function as the terminus of the system.
君たちはシステムの末端だ
That's the part that interacts with the public. It's how they recognize and understand it.
そして人々は末端を通してのみシステムを認識し理解する
Therefore, the system's credibility is judged
by how properly and strictly you are functioning.
よってシステムの信頼性とは
いかに末端が適性に厳格に機能しているかで判断される
If any of you doubt the Dominator, it could
eventually cause all citizens to doubt this society's order.
君たちがドミネーターを疑うならば
それはやがて全ての市民がこの社会の秩序を疑う発端にもなりかねない
Do you understand?
分かるかね
It seems that the report we submitted wasn't complete.
提出した報告書には 不備があったようです
Fine. Resubmit it by tomorrow morning.
結構だ 明朝までに再提出したまえ
Naturally, you'll need to prepare an
explanation that your subordinates will accept.
当然君の部下たちにも納得いく説明を用意する必要があるだろうが…
Please leave it to me.
お任せください
Good. Ginoza...
よろしい
宜野座君…
My confidence in you was indeed well-placed.
やはり君は私が見込んだとおりの人材だ
Capture Makishima Shougo.
槙島聖護の身柄を確保しろ
Isolate him from this society as soon as possible.
一日でも早くこの社会から隔離するんだ
But don't kill him.
ただし殺すな
Immediate punishment or execution requires Sibyl's involvement.
即時量刑 即時処刑はシビュラあっての制度だ
Understood.
了解しました
All you need to do is capture this man and bring him to the Bureau.
この男を捕らえ 本局にまで連行すればいい
Don't worry about the rest.
あとは何も気にするな
Makishima Shougo will never threaten society again,
槙島聖護は二度と社会を脅かすことなどなくなる
just as Touma Kouzaburou hasn't.
藤間幸三郎と同様にな
Hello.
失礼します
Hey.
Reading a book?
読書ですか
Yeah.
ああ
Thanks for taking the time to visit.
わざわざすまない
No problem.
いえ…
I was told to take some time off anyway.
どうせ私も少し休めって言われてますし
Have they had the funeral yet?
葬儀の方は
It was the day before yesterday.
一昨日に
I see.
そうか…
I'm sorry.
すみません
Why are you apologizing?
なぜ謝る
I let Makishima Shougo get away.
槙島聖護を取り逃がしました
It's not your fault.
あんたの責任じゃない
It was the Dominator that didn't work properly. Right?
おかしくなったのはドミネーターだ
そうなんだろ
They said that there was nothing wrong with the gun itself.
銃そのものには何の欠陥もなかったそうです
Inspector Ginoza's petitioning the top brass and investigating now.
今宜野座さんが上に掛け合って調べてくれてます
He's never revealed himself to us until now.
一度も尻尾を出さなかったやつだ
He might have some sort of trick.
何かからくりがあるのかもしれない
Some secret means to outwit us.
ドミネーターばかりに頼ってきた俺たちを
まんまと出し抜くための秘策が…
You're your normal self, Kougami.
いつもどおりですね　狡噛さん
あんたも思ったより立ち直りが早い
You recovered more quickly than I thought you would too.
I can't go on feeling depressed forever.
落ち込んでばかりじゃいられません
We have to capture Makishima Shougo.
槙島聖護を捕まえないと
He's the one who killed my friend.
友達の敵ですもんね
And your friend too.
私にとっても
狡噛さんにとっても…
Yeah.
そうだな
Well, I feel a little better after seeing you.
何だか安心しました
Take care.
ではお大事に
After all that, there's actually one thing that I'm relieved about.
一つだけ　ある意味ではうれしいと思えることもあります
We know Makishima Shougo really exists.
槙島聖護は実在した
No one will doubt you anymore.
もう誰も狡噛さんのことを疑いません
We can now finally pursue the same goal together.
私たち　これでようやく
一つの目標を一緒に追い掛けられるようになりました
Tsunemori will work on a photofit picture?
常守が モンタージュを？！
Right. She'll do a memory scoop.
そう メモリースクープだよ
That's a process that visualizes people's
memories by reading directly from their brain waves.
記憶にある視覚情報を脳波から直接読み取って映像化するっていう…
I heard that Akane's trying to
reconstruct what Makishima Shougo looks like.
朱ちゃん　あれで槙島聖護の姿を再現するつもりらしくて…
So far, she's the only one who's seen his face clearly.
今んとこ
槙島ってやつの顔をはっきり見たことがあるのは朱ちゃんだけだから
That procedure involves forcibly reliving one's memories!
記憶の強制的な追体験だぞ
And not just any memory — the memory
where her friend was killed before her very eyes!
よりにもよって 目の前で友人を殺された経験を…
I know! That's why everyone tried to stop her.
分かってるよ
だからみんなも止めたんだ
There's no way anyone's Psycho-Pass
would still be okay after that, not even Akane's!
いくら朱ちゃんでも サイコパスが無事で済むはずがない
Then why?!
じゃあ何で…
She said she'd bring down Makishima next time for sure.
次は絶対に仕留めるってさ
槙島を…
So in the end, I don't think you can really talk.
だとすれば
少なくともコウちゃんには彼女のことを
とやかく言う権利はないかも
Was that from Kougami?
狡噛か
Yeah. Kagari or someone probably told him what I was up to.
はい
たぶん縢君あたりがチクったんじゃないかと…
Don't you have to talk to him?
話さなくていいのか
There's no need to.
必要ないです
I'm sure he'll just try to stop me,
私を止めるつもりなんですよ
even though he's always doing reckless things himself.
自分は無茶ばっかりするくせに…
I'm against it too. It's too dangerous.
俺も反対だ
危険過ぎる
Your Psycho-Pass has already been affected.
ただでさえ君のサイコパスはダメージを受けている
At worst, your Crime Coefficient could suffer as well.
最悪の場合は犯罪係数の悪化だって…
The Bureau Chief ordered us not to conduct a public investigation, right?
局長命令で公開捜査はできないんですよね
Yeah. Either way, this is a sensitive matter.
ああ…何しろデリケートな問題だ
An expert team is investigating it.
専門のチームが調査している
Until they release their results, don't tell
anyone about what happened in the basement.
その結果が出るまで地下で起きたことは他言無用だ
We can't wait for their results.
調査の結果を待っていられません
Without investigating this publicly, it's hard to gather clues.
非公開では手掛かりは集まりにくい
We need a photofit picture.
モンタージュが必要です
But...
しかし…
I don't mind if it means my Crime Coefficient will go up.
そのために犯罪係数が上がったとしても構いません
私は執行官になってでも
I'll corner Makishima Shougo,
even if I end up as an Enforcer afterward.
槙島聖護を追い詰めます
Don't say that so lightly!
そんなことを軽々しく口にするな
Inspector Ginoza... I'll be fine.
宜野座さん…大丈夫ですよ
My resilient Psycho-Pass is the one thing I have going for me.
私ってサイコパスが曇りにくいのだけが取りえですから
Everything's set... Akane.
準備完了　朱ちゃん
Okay.
はい
I'll be monitoring your physical
condition and Psycho-Pass the entire time.
あなたの体調とサイコパスはずーっとモニタリングしてるからね
I trust you, Karanomori.
唐之杜さんを信用します
Okay, okay. Just leave it to me.
ＯＫＯＫ　お姉さんに任せてね
You'll be fine.
悪いようにはしないから
Concentrate and try to remember
the time you encountered the culprit.
犯人と遭遇したときのことをよく思い出して
Okay.
はい
When I catch a brain signal related to that memory, I'll amplify it.
その記憶に関わる脳内の信号をキャッチしたら増幅します
It will likely cause quite a bit of emotional strain, though.
かなりの精神的な負担が予想されるけど…
I'm aware of that.
覚悟の上です
Okay... Then I'll start now.
よろしい　始めるわよ
And how do you define crime to start with?
With the Dominator you're holding?
君が手にした　その銃…
ドミネーターをつかさどるシビュラシステムが決めるのか
Does the Sibyl System that governs that gun decide it?
Crime Coefficient is 48. Not a target for enforcement action.
「犯罪係数　４８」
「執行対象ではありません」
The trigger will be locked.
「トリガーをロックします」
Help! Akane!
How very regrettable, Inspector Tsunemori Akane.
とても残念だよ
常守朱監視官
Akane!
朱
Not a target for enforcement action.
「執行対象ではありません」
The trigger will be locked.
「トリガーをロックします」
Stop it!
やめてーっ
Hey!
I know!
おい
分かってる
Get a hold of yourself, Inspector Tsunemori!
しっかりしろ　常守監視官
Inspector Tsunemori!
常守監視官
Tsunemori!
常守
Tsunemori Akane!
常守朱
Sorry.
すまない
I-Inspector Ginoza...
宜野座さん…
Yeah... Are you okay?
ああ…大丈夫か
Tsunemori!
常守…
The memory scoop was successful!
メモリースクープは成功
I'll start processing the image right away!
早速イメージング処理に取り掛かるわ
How's her Psycho-Pass?!
彼女のサイコパスは
うん…大丈夫
Yeah, it's okay.
Her Hue curve is within regulation limits.
色相カーブは規定値以内 犯罪係数は…
Her Crime Coefficient is...
This is incredible!
すごいわ
It went up once, but it's already showing signs of recovery!
一度上昇したポイントが もう回復の兆しを見せている
Inspector Tsunemori...
常守監視官…
See? I told you I'd be fine, didn't I?
ねっ　平気だったでしょ
You'd go this far, huh?
君はそうまでして…
Hm?
Have you recovered from your injuries?
もうケガは大丈夫なの
I threatened my doctor.
これ以上入院させるなら
I told him that I'd set fire to the room if he kept me there any longer.
病室に火を付けるって医者を脅した
That's the Ko we know and love.
さすがコウちゃん
I was kidding. I persuaded him.
嘘だよ　説得した
More importantly, how's Inspector Tsunemori?
それより常守監視官はどうなんだ
She's undergoing a mental care session at the nurse's office.
医務室でメンタルケアのセッション中
But according to Shion's diagnosis, she'll recover soon.
でも志恩の診断では すぐに持ち直すだろうって
She might have a cute face, but that girl's got serious guts.
カワイイ顔してて根性据わってるっていうか…
It freaked me out, to be honest.
正直ビビったわ
After all she went through, her
Psycho-Pass didn't even enter the red zone.
あれでサイコパスがレッドゾーンいかないってんだから
What were they planning to do if something happened?!
何かあったらどうするつもりだったんだ
You're not the only one who was worried.
心配してたのはあなただけじゃないわ
But in this case, the risk paid off.
でもね危険を冒しただけの成果は上がってるわよ
So this is...
Makishima Shougo.
これが…
槙島聖護
We immediately contacted Ousou Academy... and bingo.
早速桜霜学園にも問い合わせたけど　ビンゴ
Staff and students at the Academy have testified
that this man is Shibata Yukimori, their art instructor.
教職員も生徒も揃って
Makishima Shougo
Shibata Yukimori
この男が美術科講師の柴田幸盛だと証言している
Makishima Shougo
Shibata Yukimori
This alone is enough to bring him in
as a key witness in Ouryou Rikako's case.
これだけでも 王陵璃華子の事件について
重要参考人として引っ張れる
Right now, we're doing a search through the
records of all the cameras in town, one by one.
今もね 街じゅうのカメラの録画記録に片っ端から検索かけてるよ
And one place we've already been able to find record of him was,
早速ヒットしたのがさ
believe it or not, the entrance to
Sugawara Shouko's apartment building.
何と菅原昭子のマンションのエントランス
Remember her? Spooky Boogie,
the victim in the Talisman incident.
ほら覚えてる スプーキーブーギー
タリスマン事件の犠牲者の
We've already requested a priority
search order with facial recognition.
フェイスレコグニションの優先手配も済ませてる
Next time he makes a move,
we'll receive a report immediately.
次にこいつが動きを起こせば
即座にこっちに通報が届くわ
Tsunemori is...
常守は…
She's already a full-fledged detective.
あいつは…もういっぱしのデカだ
To think that you want to talk to me.
お前が俺を呼び出すなんて
What next, is it gonna snow tomorrow?
こりゃ～あしたは雪かな
The chance of precipitation all day tomorrow is zero.
明日の降水確率は昼夜共にゼロだ
That's an expression from the old days, all right? Geez.
昔からある言い回しだろうよ まったく
So, what happened?
で　何があった
I have some questions about Inspector Tsunemori.
常守監視官のことで 幾つか質問が…
What about her?
お嬢ちゃんがどうした
Why doesn't her Hue ever get clouded?
なぜ あいつの色相は濁らないんだ
How does she manage her stress?
どんなストレスケアを
You're asking me about that?
それを俺に聞くかね
You're closer to her than I am, aren't you?
俺よりは親しく接してるだろ
I don't have the answer.
分からんよ
Well, one thing I know for sure is that
she isn't afraid of her Crime Coefficient at all.
まあ 一つはっきり言えるのは
お嬢ちゃんは自分の犯罪係数をまったく恐れていないってことさ
She is, how should I put it...
あの子は何ていうかその…
She accepts things as they are.
物事を良しとしている
She forgives society, acknowledges it, and accepts it.
世の中を許して　認めて　受け入れている
On top of that, she doesn't mind taking risks, so it's not like she's just going with the flow.
それでいて危ない橋を渡るのもいとわないんだから
ただ流れに身を任せているわけでもない
She probably believes unquestioningly
in the meaning and the value of being a detective.
刑事っていう仕事の意味と価値を疑うことなく信じてるんだな
Are you saying things were different for you?
あんたの場合は違ったっていうのか
Me? Hmm...
俺か　ふん…そうだな
Well...
I might be like this now, but I feel
like I shared her belief in justice long ago.
こんな俺でも昔はあの子みたいに正義とかいうもんを信じていたような気がする
But one day, I was suddenly given a gun that speaks,
ところがある日いきなり 言葉をしゃべる銃を渡されて
and I was told that from then on I just had to shoot when it told me to in order to capture or kill people.
これからはそいつの言いなりになって人を撃ち
捕まえるなり　殺すなりしろと命令された
I was angry.
腹が立ったよ
That wasn't the detective work that I believed in.
こんなやり方は俺が信じた刑事の仕事じゃない
The more I felt that way, the cloudier my Psycho-Pass became.
そう思えば思うほどサイコパスも曇っていった
If you had that many doubts...
そこまで疑問があったなら
why didn't you quit being a detective?
どうして刑事を辞めなかった
あんたはそんな不本意な生き方のために
Why did you make Mom and I pay the price when you didn't even want to live that way?
俺を…母さんを巻き添えにしたのか
Damn you!
ふざけやがって…
How dare you complain about it now?
いまさらどの面下げて泣き言をほざくんだ
You're right.
まったくだよ
I keep saying I don't like it, but I'm still a detective even now.
嫌だ嫌だと言いながら
結局俺は 今でも刑事のままだ
You denied Sibyl... and Sibyl denied you.
あんたはシビュラを否定し
シビュラはあんたを否定した
A new order was born, and the country moved on without you.
そして新しい秩序が生まれ
この国だけが立ち直った
Yeah. After all, I might've been wrong.
ああ…結局は俺が間違っていたのかもしれん
Around the time I accepted this era and came
to terms with it, my Crime Coefficient stabilized.
今の時代を認めて 諦めがついた頃合いに
俺の犯罪係数は横ばいになった
It was more than a little too late, though.
まあいささか以上に手遅れだったが…
So, what about you?
で　お前はどうなんだ
Have you been able to maintain
a nice clear color on your Psycho-Pass?
サイコパス　ちゃんとクリアカラーで維持できてるか
I don't see why you need to worry about that.
あんたに心配される筋合いじゃない
What, are you trying to act like a father now?
いまさら父親面しようっていうのか
What's wrong with a subordinate showing concern
for his boss? Especially one who's due for a promotion?
出世を控えた上司を部下が気遣って何が悪い
Just like you were saying earlier...
お前がさっき俺に言ったとおりだ
If you question your job...
この仕事に疑問があるなら
If you start feeling that something is amiss, be careful.
何か疑わしいと思うようなことを抱え込んだら気を付けろ
Once you start down that path,
you might run into the same pitfall as I did.
そこから先には
俺がはまったのと同じ落とし穴が待ち構えているかもしれん
There's no way I could love anyone,
Dareka wo aisuru koto nante
Dekiru wake nakutte
But I wish to be loved by someone in turn
The world may not have
Dakedo dareka ni aisaretakute
Ended yesterday after all,
Kawaranai kinou ga zutto tsuzuita to shite mo
But we will not budge
Doko ni mo ike ya shinainda
watashi to kimi
From where we are
Kamisama doko he itte shimatta no nee
God, in favor of which parts have you left us?
Henji wa nakute itsu datte sou da yo
I receive no reply, I never do
Are you still here?
You'll never walk alone
I walk with you
Anata to iku
Donna tsumi mo
I will share all your sins
Seotte ageru
Together with you
Michi naki michi wo
Aruiteku no
I walk
A trackless path
Anata to futari de
You've finally been identified.
とうとう面が割れちゃったね
You're at the end of your rope, Shougo.
後がないよ　聖護君
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This is a world where the mental state and
personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed,
these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are
commonly called "Psycho-Pass".